The next piece of C that you are going to learn about is functions.
接下来你要学习的C部分是函数。
To see why they are so important,
要了解它们为何如此重要，
let us take a look back at our closestPoint algorithm.
让我们回顾一下我们的 ClosestPoint 算法。
There are two places here where this algorithm computes the distance between two points.
这里有两个地方使用此算法计算两点之间的距离。
Why is that important?
为什么这很重要？
Well, we need to do the same computation twice.
好吧，我们需要进行两次相同的计算。
Without functions, we would write the same code twice and that is just in this problem.
如果没有函数，我们会写两次相同的代码，而这仅仅是这个问题。
What if we have other problems that also need to compute the distance between two points?
如果我们还有其他问题需要计算两点之间的距离怎么办？
We have a few examples of other problems that would
我们有几个其他问题的例子，
need to compute the distance between two points,
需要计算两点之间的距离，
but there are many others.
但还有很多其他问题。
We could rewrite the code each time,
我们可以每次都重写代码，对于
which may not seem like a big deal for something as small as computing
像计算
the distance but we want to avoid duplicating code whenever possible.
距离这样小的事情来说，这似乎没什么大不了的，但我们希望尽可能避免重复代码。
Every time we rewrite code,
每次我们重写代码时，
we run the risk of making mistakes and introducing bugs into our program.
我们都会冒着犯错误和在程序中引入错误的风险。
Furthermore, it is really boring to rewrite the same code again and again.
此外，一次又一次地重写同样的代码真的很无聊。
Instead, we should abstract the computation for distance out into a function of its own.
相反，我们应该将距离的计算抽象成一个自己的函数。将@@
Making distance its own function means we can reuse
距离设为自己的函数意味着我们可以在
that algorithm any place we need it without rewriting it. How would this work?
任何需要的地方重复使用该算法，而无需重写它。这将如何运作？
Well, our closestPoint function would,
好吧，我们的 ClosestPoint 函数将在
in its code, call the distance function.
其代码中调用距离函数。
That is, it would ask the distance function to perform its computation.
也就是说，它将要求距离函数执行其计算。
To do this, our closestPoint function would first pass in
为此，我们的 ClosestPoint 函数将首先传入
parameter values specifying which points the distance function should compute on.
参数值，指定距离函数应在哪些点上进行计算。
The distance function would execute its code,
距离函数将执行其代码，
doing whatever statements are in it according to the rules you are learning.
根据你正在学习的规则执行其中的任何语句。
It finishes when it comes up with
当它得出
an answer which returns back to the function that called it.
一个答案并返回到调用它的函数时，它就结束了。
When it returns, the distance function is done
当它返回时，距离函数就完成了
and the calling function continues its own execution,
，调用函数会继续自己执行，
making use of the answer it got from the function it called.
使用它从调用的函数中得到的答案。
So how is this helpful?
那么，这有什么帮助呢？
First, we can reuse this distance computation any time we need.
首先，我们可以随时重复使用这种距离计算。
We don't have to rewrite it.
我们不必重写它。
We can just call the distance function to compute the distance between any two points.
我们可以调用距离函数来计算任意两点之间的距离。
Whether we need to compute the distance at the various places in
无论我们需要计算C
the closestPoint function or in
losestPoint函数中不同位置的距离，还是在我们要
some other problem we are solving doesn't matter, we just call it.
解决的其他问题中计算距离都无关紧要，我们只需要称之为即可。
The other important benefit of functions is the abstraction.
函数的另一个重要好处是抽象。
Abstraction is the separation of the interface,
抽象是将接口（
meaning what something does,
意思是某物所做的事情）与
from its implementation, meaning how it does it.
其实现的分离，即它是如何实现的。
Once we have written the distance function,
一旦我们编写了距离函数，
we can just make use of it without thinking about its inner workings.
我们就可以在不考虑其内部工作原理的情况下使用它。
As you build larger and larger programs,
随着你构建越来越大的程序，
abstraction becomes more and more important.
抽象变得越来越重要。
You aren't limited to two functions either.
您也不局限于两个功能。
You can have many functions which can call as many other functions as they need to.
你可以有许多函数，它们可以根据需要调用任意数量的其他函数。
For example, suppose our closestPoint function were part of a much larger program,
例如，假设我们的 ClosestPoint 函数是一个更大的程序的一部分，
which has information about various types of locations and
该程序包含有关各种类型位置
uses that information to give us the nearest location of a particular type.
的信息，并使用这些信息为我们提供特定类型的最近位置。
You might end up with something like this.
你最终可能会得到这样的结果。
The main function, which is where all C programs start,
主函数是所有 C 程序的起点，它
might call a function to find the store nearest point 42,17,
可能会调用一个函数来查找最近的商店点 42,17，并
passing in parameters to specify this information.
传入参数来指定此信息。
That function might then call another function to find all locations whose type is store.
然后，该函数可能会调用另一个函数来查找所有类型为 store 的位置。然后
The getByType function could then return back a list of
，getByType 函数可以返回
locations for stores which findNearest can then use.
商店的位置列表，然后 findNearest 可以使用。
It is totally fine for findNearest to then call another function
然后，findNearest 可以调用另一个函数（
such as our closestPoint function to find the point nearest the location we want.
例如我们的 ClosestPoint 函数）来找到离我们想要的位置最近的点。
As we previously discussed,
正如我们之前所讨论的，C
closestPoint can call distance to compute the distance
losestPoint可以调用距离来计算
between two points and it will return back the distance it computed.
两点之间的距离，它将返回计算出的距离。
Of course, it is totally fine for closestPoint to
当然，对于ClosestPoint来说，
call distance as many times as it needs,
根据需要多次呼叫距离，
getting back the answer for whatever points it passed in.
无论传入什么分数都能得到答案，这是完全可以的。
When closestPoint finishes its computation and figures out its answer,
当 ClosestPoint 完成计算并找出答案时，
it returns that value to the function that called it which then
它会将该值返回给调用
finishes its computation and returns its answer to the function that called it.
它的函数，然后该函数完成计算并将其答案返回给调用它的函数。
Okay, great.
好吧，太棒了。
Now, you have the high-level concepts of functions.
现在，你有了函数的高级概念。
Let's dive into their syntax and semantics in C.
让我们在 C 语言中深入研究它们的语法和语义